JOSE DAVID GALE TORRE

FrontEnd Developer



Dublin, Ireland. Phone: 083 (209) 4639



josedavidgale@gmail.com



JdgaleTorre



josedavidgale.vercel.app/

SKILL'S















Graphql











SCRUM

SOCIAL



Linkedin josedavidgale

CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES

Front End Web Developer Nanodegree (2018)

view certificate
(https://confirm.udacity.com/EWPDCHSP)

ABOUT ME

I'm a software developer from Honduras; I've been working since 2011 as a developer for a pharmacy. I came to Dublin to improve my English and growth. I'm open to help with any task you need. I like the cook, although I never took a cooking class. I'm looking forward to working together.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Jan 2009 - Nov 2011

Developer at ITNova

Develop system for a pharmacy Install CCTV on differents company Develop system for Human Resources

O Nov 2011 - Oct 2020

Developer/Scrum Master at Grupo Farsiman

Integrated Payment with BAC Bank
Developed system of GiftCards
Lead team of Developers as Scrum Master
Migrate different systems to Angular, for a better user
experience

O Apr 2021 - Jan 2022

Full Stack Developer at Code Exitos

Improved the user experience on the rental process on Jobbox

Implemented changes on user experiences on Quotient App

EDUCATION

Q 2015

Master on Business Management United

o 2011

Bachelor of Computer Science

Universidad Catolica de Honduras